

# Joseph Tongay

joseph.tongay@gmail.com 512-293-9823

Austin, TX

# Full-Stack Web Developer

A 10 year restaurant industry veteran turned Full-Stack Web Developer with a curious mind and a will to learn any new technology. Strong focus in Test Driven Development, JavaScript Fundamentals, and Problem Solving. Able to bring positive energy, entertainment, and productivity to any group.

### Education

Galvanize - Web Development Immersive August 2016 - January 2017

## Skills

JavaScript	HTML	Bootstrap	React
Node.js	CSS	Heroku	Typescript
Angular 1~4	SASS	Git	SQL
Express	AJAX	TDD	Ruby on Rails

# **Projects**

### **Power Ranking**

GitHub Front-End GitHub Back-End

Web Application where a user can vote on their top three and least favorite items in any given topic and generate score. The score can also be generated through Twitter by tweeting at the official Power Ranking App.

Tech Stack:

Node.js • Express • Angular 2 • Postgres • Bootstrap

#### Raspberry Pi Smart TV

Created a Smart TV using a Raspberry Pi and a hybrid app, where a user can install Node on their Raspberry Pi, clone the repository, input their IP address in the app, search for a video and hit play.

Tech Stack:

Node.js • Express • Socket.io • Ionic • Raspberry Pi

# Experience

Netspend - Front End QA Engineer February 2017 - Present

Participated in every aspect of the development cycle including sprint planning, sprint grooming, and demonstration's to product owners. Created and maintained the selenium/cucumber front end automation suite when new and updated features are implemented. Participated in code reviews and offered assistance to improve the front end application's

Galvanize - Web Development Immersive August 2016 - January 2017

Built numerous Web Applications and participated in all exercises to further develop skills necessary for continuation of the program. Emulated different styles of workflow like paired programming, group programming, and solo research.